Hello friends, in the previous video I
told you
how to get Flipkart gift card through Bajaj and now
in this video I will tell you how you will
redeem it.  Many people do it in a hurry.
They do
not get Flipkart gift card because they do
not know how to get it.  Ok?  I
can show you my earlier video.
How can you get it and
how will you redeem it after getting it.  Let me tell you.
In this you will get OT plays.
This is a Flipkart gift voucher of ₹500 and
in this, you will get more than ₹50 on paying electricity bill,
mobile recharge, DTSC recharge, gas
booking
and you get 12 OTTs in it.
After that you are seeing
how you will redeem the gift voucher of Flipkart.
I will tell you the complete process in this.
Many people do it in a hurry.
Then they say we did
not receive the gift card.  So that is their own fault.
Watch my previous video to see how you can
get it.  I will tell you in detail in this video
how you will redeem it.
From here we copy it.
We have to copy the Flipkart voucher and redeem it from here.
I am making it on my other phone
because screen
recording is not allowed on Bajaj.  So
I am making a video for you by logging in from another phone.
After copying it from here, we will redeem it as
Flipkart gift voucher.
Copy it from here.  Enter the promo code that
we have copied.  Here we will
enter our mobile number which is your registered
mobile number with which you had registered in Bajaj.
Ok?  Through which
you got it.
After giving your mobile number here,
as soon as you register it, you will receive an OTP.
OTP will come on our registered mobile number.
Now we submit this OTP on it.
I will show you what interface is shown to us after submitting.
We submitted it.  After this, we are shown a
Flipkart gift voucher.  It is worth ₹500.
Now we will redeem it.
How to redeem?  Look, this is how it has to be done.
This Flipkart is showing you ₹500 above.
We will do one on this quantity.  Correct?
We will fill everything on this like our mobile number and name.
After that,
as soon as we proceed with it, we will have to enter our email address
in it.  So first you make your
quantity one in this.  Write your name,
whatever your name is.
Ok?  You can write any name.  Rest
write your own name.  After that we will
write our name etc. on it and then write our email address on it.
what would it be?  With this, we will receive this gift card voucher
on our registered mobile number through SMS
or through mail.
After that we will
go directly to Flipkart app.   Will
run later in Flipkart's app.  This is
our arrival.  Yes, look, our gift card has arrived.  The
value of this gift card is
₹500.  We can buy anything with this on Flipkart.
Clothes, electronics items,
grocery items, anything.  This is our gift
voucher number and this is its PIN.  Now
I will tell you how to redeem it
on Flipkart.  Ok?  I will tell you its total details.
How much money can I save you even after the full bill is paid?  I
will explain everything in this video and show you how I do shopping with this money.
Look at this.  Let's
go to Flipkart.  These are my items
that I have already selected.  Ok
?  Now we will do this.  Let's place orders.
You can see all this.  You
can order whatever you want.  You can use Flipkart's
gift voucher for anything.
We will continue here.
I already have a gift card of ₹89.
In this we will
select this.  Ok?  My bill was something like ₹930.   That's how much
happened to him.  Now look at our gift
card which we have received from Bajaj.   Here it is.
We will write it here, copy it and
paste it there.  Ok?
Here we pasted the gift card.
Below is the voucher pin 1887
type it below enter voucher pin
ok.
Gift card is written below all the payments.  Ok?
What is our balance now?  ₹347 means that our
gift card of ₹500 was used.  Many
people say it doesn't happen.  I say it is 1
lakh%.  Ok?  How do we save more money after that
?  After that we will go
to Chrome.  There we will search for
Flipkart Gift Card.  What happens many times
?  Flipkart gift card Uhu is done,
deal is done and what do you say?  We have Paytm
through which we get gift cards at very cheap rates i.e.
we get some percentage discount
on them.  Here at DELG I got a
₹250 gift card for ₹46.  Ok?
We pay for it again.  Like I
show you.  Search for deals here.   I have a
lot of
gift cards here, I can cancel it.  Whatever the payment amount, a
discount of 2-3% is available every time.
And these are trusted apps.   There is
no chance of any money getting stuck on these.
Whatever the amount is, do it for example ₹1000.   Will
you do some shopping worth ₹500?
Use it again next time.  In this we saved ₹5
again.  Some items have a selected
amount like ₹500, ₹1700, ₹1800, by
filling that we can get it.  The rest will remain there, no
problem.
Comes in handy at the next stopping.  This ₹240 is still our savings.
Ok?  Now we pay for it.
That gift card of ours has also been used.
How will this gift card be used?
Both its code and PIN also came.  We
paste it there.
Here comes the card number.  The gift card will be
written here.  You can send as many
gift cards as you want, any kind of gift card, but it should be from
Flipkart.
You can avail the benefit by submitting that gift card.
Well then.  In this video of mine you came to
know that this video is true.  In this you
get a ₹500 gift card.  12 platforms
OTT are available.  You get a lot for free.   It is
your benefit that everyone does shopping.  But there is a
time limit on it.  Maybe you get Rs 80 for a few
days.  It has to be redeemed within 80 days.
Now after that
our payment etc. everything has been successful.
Ok?   For this
we pay ₹97.
We paid for this.  If you like the video,
I will post more good videos on this channel.
Subscribe to my channel
, support, share.  See you
in the next good video.   I will
make more good videos.  Maybe
you will like it very much.  Look, the ₹500
gift card that I received from Bajaj has been
redeemed.  See you on the next
video.  Until then, take care of yourself and
be happy.   In the
next video,
I will tell you what base you want.  How to talk to customer care
on call in one go.